Kristopher Kohlmeier

Production Technologies

kristopherkohlmeier@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/kris-kohlmeier kristopherkohlmeier.com +1 805-276-4713 Camarillo, California, 93010, United States

Four years of experience troubleshooting and setting up computer systems and equipment in live production environments. Proven track record of quickly solving various technical issues in mission-critical environments and bringing in new technologies to elevate production workflows.

Work Experience

Production Technology Lead

Crossroads Church | Camarillo

Jun 2021 - Present

- Oversaw and maintained all hardware and software related to live productions on-site.
- Led over \$50, 000 in projects and efforts to improve and maintain production systems.
- Quickly resolved hardware and software failures during live events, keeping production running smoothly and preventing services from halting.
- Led and grew a team of production volunteers, training, coordinating, and supporting team members by onboarding systems and technologies that improved production quality and setup efficiency.
- Provided general IT support for staff members across the facility, running with small projects to improve and update computer systems on-site.

Animation Technology Intern

Jun 2023 - Aug 2023

Skydance Animation Studios | Santa Monica

- Learned the pipeline process for CG movies from start to finish.
- Assisted pipeline engineers by developing a custom script to audit their codebase.
- Worked with systems engineers to integrate a studio-wide printing system and created SOPs for the system.
- Created a tracking document for all editorial hardware, assisting the media engineering team during studio location changes.
- Solved Jira tickets for the IT help desk and set up a fleet of new machines with their MDM software.

Core Skills

Dante Certified, Stage Lighting Consoles, Live audio mixers, Pro-presenter, Davinci Resolve, Multi-Camera Broadcast, Python, C/C++, Javascript, HTML/CSS, Vue.js, React, Linux, MacOS, Windows

Education

California State University

Jan 2021 - Jun 2024

Bachelor of Science Computer Science

Relevant Coursework: Dance Production Team, Image Processing, Operating Systems, Computer Networking